[{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664057427,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":16654,"timeElapsed":81200},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664064165,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":6736,"timeElapsed":87938},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664071883,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":7718,"timeElapsed":95656},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664078922,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":7037,"timeElapsed":102695},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664084556,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":5632,"timeElapsed":108328},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664089388,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":4831,"timeElapsed":113161},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664094226,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":4837,"timeElapsed":117999},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664101555,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":7328,"timeElapsed":125328},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664105939,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":4384,"timeElapsed":129712},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664116897,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"108","question":"What are some pieces of media (books, movies, music, etc.) that have influenced how you think or see the world?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":8728,"timeElapsed":140670},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664122834,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"108","question":"What are some pieces of media (books, movies, music, etc.) that have influenced how you think or see the world?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":5935,"timeElapsed":146607},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664130859,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"108","question":"What are some pieces of media (books, movies, music, etc.) that have influenced how you think or see the world?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":8024,"timeElapsed":154632},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664136305,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"108","question":"What are some pieces of media (books, movies, music, etc.) that have influenced how you think or see the world?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":5445,"timeElapsed":160078},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664141676,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"108","question":"What are some pieces of media (books, movies, music, etc.) that have influenced how you think or see the world?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":5369,"timeElapsed":165449},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664147013,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"108","question":"What are some pieces of media (books, movies, music, etc.) that have influenced how you think or see the world?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":5337,"timeElapsed":170786},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664152691,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"108","question":"What are some pieces of media (books, movies, music, etc.) that have influenced how you think or see the world?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":5677,"timeElapsed":176464},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664158471,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"108","question":"What are some pieces of media (books, movies, music, etc.) that have influenced how you think or see the world?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":5778,"timeElapsed":182244},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664163677,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"108","question":"What are some pieces of media (books, movies, music, etc.) that have influenced how you think or see the world?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":5205,"timeElapsed":187450},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664173538,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":8064,"timeElapsed":197311},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664180405,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":6866,"timeElapsed":204178},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664185187,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4781,"timeElapsed":208960},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664189647,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4459,"timeElapsed":213420},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664193958,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":4309,"timeElapsed":217731},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664197753,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":3794,"timeElapsed":221526},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664202563,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":4808,"timeElapsed":226336},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664206786,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4222,"timeElapsed":230559},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664215003,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":8215,"timeElapsed":238776},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664226626,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":7104,"timeElapsed":250399},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664230702,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4076,"timeElapsed":254475},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664236176,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5473,"timeElapsed":259949},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664241121,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4944,"timeElapsed":264894},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664246160,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":5037,"timeElapsed":269933},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664249621,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3460,"timeElapsed":273394},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664253610,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3989,"timeElapsed":277383},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664259444,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5832,"timeElapsed":283217},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664265441,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5997,"timeElapsed":289214},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664276889,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":9826,"timeElapsed":300662},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664281887,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":4996,"timeElapsed":305660},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664288367,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":6479,"timeElapsed":312140},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664294670,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":6302,"timeElapsed":318443},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664302495,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":7824,"timeElapsed":326268},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664305439,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2942,"timeElapsed":329212},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664308775,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":3335,"timeElapsed":332548},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664313081,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":4304,"timeElapsed":336854},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664320679,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":7597,"timeElapsed":344452},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664325120,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4440,"timeElapsed":348892},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664338572,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":11415,"timeElapsed":362345},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664342645,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4072,"timeElapsed":366418},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664351336,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":8690,"timeElapsed":375109},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664356310,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":4973,"timeElapsed":380083},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664359485,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3174,"timeElapsed":383258},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664363719,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":4232,"timeElapsed":387492},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664367120,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":3400,"timeElapsed":390893},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664375531,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":8410,"timeElapsed":399304},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664378491,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":2958,"timeElapsed":402264},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664392505,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":12417,"timeElapsed":416278},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664397027,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4520,"timeElapsed":420800},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664401234,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":4206,"timeElapsed":425007},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664407094,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":5860,"timeElapsed":430867},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664410097,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3002,"timeElapsed":433870},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664415091,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4993,"timeElapsed":438864},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664418634,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3542,"timeElapsed":442407},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664422970,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":4336,"timeElapsed":446743},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664427708,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":4737,"timeElapsed":451481},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664430885,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":3176,"timeElapsed":454658},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664445349,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":11964,"timeElapsed":469122},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664450405,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":5055,"timeElapsed":474178},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664458084,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":7680,"timeElapsed":481857},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664463325,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":5240,"timeElapsed":487098},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664466902,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":3576,"timeElapsed":490675},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664470416,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":3513,"timeElapsed":494189},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664473750,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3332,"timeElapsed":497523},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664479199,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":5448,"timeElapsed":502972},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664482789,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":3589,"timeElapsed":506562},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664491400,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":6871,"timeElapsed":515173},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664499505,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":8104,"timeElapsed":523278},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664504815,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":5310,"timeElapsed":528588},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664511262,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":6445,"timeElapsed":535035},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664514252,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":2990,"timeElapsed":538025},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664517293,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":3040,"timeElapsed":541066},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664520371,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":3077,"timeElapsed":544144},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664527106,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":6735,"timeElapsed":550879},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664531395,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":4287,"timeElapsed":555168},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664542755,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":9557,"timeElapsed":566528},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664549682,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":6927,"timeElapsed":573455},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664554352,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4669,"timeElapsed":578125},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664562614,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":8260,"timeElapsed":586387},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664566578,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":3963,"timeElapsed":590351},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664569540,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2961,"timeElapsed":593313},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664573445,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":3905,"timeElapsed":597218},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664578171,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4724,"timeElapsed":601944},{"subjectID":"m1g9o9kbjv","prolificID":"5d31c201c88f0e001a4c3cb3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421521f5a0ffaf673ee22","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664582037,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3866,"timeElapsed":605810}]